That was the 10th time I've peed here.
我已經上了十次廁所
It's also the 10th time you've told us.
你也跟我們說了十次
Sorry,it must be hard to hear.
抱歉，你們一定聽得很煩
It's easier having babies playing "Bring in Da Funk" on your bladder!
三個寶寶在你的膀胱上 蹦蹦跳跳比較好玩
I am so sick of being pregnant. God!
我真是受夠懷孕了
I can't sleep,except on my back, which hurt. So I can't sleep.
我睡不著，除非睡床上 但是又會痛，等於睡不著
My only happiness is from a cup of coffee...
我唯一的樂趣來自咖啡
...which is decaf because I'm pregnant!
但它是低咖啡因的因為我懷孕
You want a cookie?
菲比，你要吃餅乾嗎？
Thank you so much!
太謝謝你了
So,honey,how are those mood swings coming?
你的情緒起伏還好嗎？
I haven't had any yet.
我還沒有這個困擾
The One with the Worst Best Man Ever
本集播出：「史上最差伴郎」
rainystar壓制iPod-MP4
Hey,guys.
All right,here's the ring.
這就是戒指
Yes,yes! A thousand times,yes!
我願意，我願意，千百個願意
Any ideas for the bachelor party?
單身派對有想法了嗎？
Before rings and bachelor parties,you have to decide who your best man will be.
托管戒指辦派對前 應該先選個伴郎吧？
Oh,it's awkward.
真尷尬，尷尬尷尬
I already asked Chandler.
我已經找錢德了
He got to do it at your first wedding.
什麼？你上次結婚他就當過了
I figured you'd understand. I've known him longer.
我以為你會瞭解 我們認識比較久
I don't have any brothers. I'll never be a best man.
拜託啦，我沒有兄弟 我永遠都沒機會了
You can be the best man when I get married.
你可以當我的伴郎
I'll never get to be a best man!
我沒機會了啦
Wait,wait.
等一下
So you'll be my best man twice, and I won't be yours at all?
我讓你當兩次 你一次也不讓我當？
Of course,you can be my best man.
你當然可以當我的伴郎
-What about me? You said I could. -I'm not getting married!
那我呢？你說我可以當 我又沒有要結婚
It's a question for science-fiction writers.
那是科幻小說要挑戰的題材
I can't believe it's not me.
你居然不找我
-How could it not be me? -I'm not even
你怎麼可以不找我？ 我又沒要… 我又沒要…
You know what? That's it.
好了，夠了
From now on, Joey will be my best man.
喬伊，從現在起你當我的伴郎
Shame about you,though.
帥！不過你真的很爛
-Stop it. -What?
別鬧 怎麼了？
One of the babies is kicking.
有個寶寶在踢
That's a good thing.
那不是好事嗎？
It's not kicking me. It's kicking another baby.
不是踢我，是踢另一個寶寶
Don't make me come in there!
別逼我進去
Do you have a big bowl I can borrow?
有碗公可以借我嗎？
There's one under the cabinet.
檯子下面有一個
-Why do you need it? -We're having a party tomorrow night.
幹嘛？ 我們明天要開派對，回見
-Are you planning on inviting us? -No. Later!
你們有打算要找我們嗎？ 沒有，回見
Get your ass back here,Tribbiani!
崔比亞尼，給我滾回來
Hormones.
荷爾蒙
How come you're having a party and we're not invited?
菲比的意思是 你們開派對怎麼不找我們？
-It's Ross' bachelor party. -So?
那是羅斯的單身派對 所以呢？
Are you bachelors?
你們是單身漢嗎？ 不是
Are you strippers?
你們是脫衣舞孃嗎？ 不是
Then you're not invited.
那就抱歉了
Then you're not invited to our party either.
那你們也別想參加我們的派對
What party?
什麼派對？
Phoebe's baby shower.
菲比的送禮會
Baby shower? That so doesn't sound like something I want to do.
送禮會？ 聽起來就很不想參加，回見
I can't believe I'm going to have a party.
你們居然要幫我辦派對
That's so great. A party!
太棒了，派對耶
I don't know why.
我也不懂
This is what I got going for the party liquor-wise.
在酒方面我的計劃是
-Get a lot of liquor. -Great.
買一大堆酒 很好
In terms of the invite list, I got you,me and Chandler.
至於邀請名單有你、我、錢德
I'll invite Gunther because we're talking pretty loud.
我會請阿甘 因為我們討論得很大聲
I'll be there.
我會去
I know it's your party...
派對是為你辦的
...but I'd like to limit the number of museum geeks.
但我想限制博物館怪腳的人數
Let's not invite any anthropologists. Just the dinosaur dudes.
那就別找人類學家 找搞恐龍的就好
We'll need a six-pack of Zima.
好，還得買半打汽水酒
Hey,what are you doing?
你們在幹嘛？
Just planning my bachelor party with my best man.
跟我的伴郎籌劃我的單身派對
Good luck trying to top the last one.
祝你們辦得比上次好
It won't be that difficult since this one won't be...
不難，因為這次
...in the basement of a Pizza Hut.
不會辦在必勝客的地下室
I'm Ross,I'm Ross. I'm too good for the Hut.
我是羅斯，必勝客配不上我
I gotta go pick up Ben. Everything sounds great.
我得去接兒子，看樣子沒問題
Keep it on the mellow side. A few guys hanging out.
總之不要太瘋，大家聚聚打牌
-No strippers or anything. -You got it.
不要找脫衣舞孃，好嗎？ 沒問題
See you later.
待會見
Have fun planning your mellow party.
好好辦不能瘋的派對吧
There will be strippers. He didn't say anything about no strippers.
會有脫衣舞孃，他沒說不要
He just said,"No strippers."
他剛就說不要
I chose not to hear that.
我當做沒聽到
Look what I got,look what I got!
你看我買了什麼
They make these for little people!
居然有這種童裝
Little Village People.
給鄉下小孩穿的
Look at this one. This is my favorite.
你看這件，我最喜歡這件
That is so sweet.
太可愛了
Phoebe will love dressing them.
菲比一定會很喜歡打扮他們
Except she won't be the one who gets to dress them.
但到時替他們打扮的不是她
She won't get to keep the babies.
因為她不能把寶寶留著
My God,we are throwing the most depressing baby shower!
天哪 這真是最令人沮喪的送禮會
Unless we give her all gifts she can use after her pregnancy.
除非送她產後可以用的禮物
Like regular coffee. Tequila!
像普通咖啡，龍舌蘭 一整盒煙
-A carton of cigarettes! -She doesn't smoke.
一整盒煙？ 她又不抽煙
-It's the thought that counts. -It's a great idea.
心意最重要 好主意
And those leather pants she's always wanted!
還有她一直想要的皮褲
She'll love that!
她一定會很高興
What the hell is this?
這是什麼玩意？
You thought it'd make me feel better?
送我2個月後才能用的禮物
To give me something I can't use for two months?
我的心情會好嗎？
This sucks!
爛透了
-Who gave me this? -Well,l
這是誰送的？ 我…我…
They told me you like them.
她們說你喜歡
All right,then I'm wrong. It's a great gift. The best present I ever got!
好吧，我錯了 這是我收過最棒的禮物
What's my next present?
下一個禮物呢？
We don't have anything.
我們都沒帶
All right,fine,then this is over.
好吧，送禮會結束
Balloons!
真是的…放什麼汽球
-Listen,about the stripper.... -Yeah?
對了，那個脫衣舞孃…
Good call!
叫得好
So I'll be hosting your next bachelor party?
知道下次要找誰辦了吧
Joey,I'm kind of hoping this will be my last one.
我希望這是最後一次
A little announcement.
請注意
I've decided that my best man is my best friend Gunther.
我決定我的伴郎 是我最要好的朋友阿甘
What's my last name?
我姓什麼？
Central Perk?
中央咖啡館？
Thanks for not marrying Rachel.
謝謝你沒娶瑞秋
Hey,Gunther! Don't forget your shirt.
阿甘，記得拿衣服
What are those?
那是什麼？
Little party favors. Check it out.
派對小贈品，你看
（98羅斯蓋勒單身派對）
（伴郎喬伊崔比亞尼）
Just want everybody to know the position of my best man is still open.
請注意，我的伴郎人選還空著
So is the position of the bride.
新娘人選也是
Great.
很好
Smooth,man.
有一套
You got some chili on your neck.
你的脖子沾到辣椒
I just want to say thanks,everyone. This was great!
謝謝大家，今晚很愉快
See you guys Monday morning.
星期一早上見
-Thanks,Joey. -Don't forget your shirt.
喬伊，謝了 別忘了拿衣服
Hey,museum geeks! Party's over.
博物館怪胎，派對結束了
Wave bye-bye to the nice lady. There you go.
跟小姐說再見，快點
Back to your parents' basement. All right.
回爸媽的地下室去
Boys,come on out. Here you go.
出來吧，來
Look at the birdies! Are those yours?
好可愛喔，是你養的？
They let you keep chickens and ducks as pets?
我不知道可以養雞鴨當寵物
And I got the duck totally trained too.
我把鴨子訓練得很好，你看
Stare at the wall.
盯著牆壁
Hardly move.
幾乎不動
Be white.
白白的
You are good at that.
你真行
I had fun tonight.
今晚很愉快
-You throw one hell of a party. -Thanks. It was great meeting you.
派對辦得很棒 謝了，很高興認識你
If any of my friends ever get married or have a birthday or a Tuesday....
要是我有朋友要結婚 或是過生日、過星期日…
Yeah,that'd be great.
那就太好了
So,I guess,good night.
那就再見了
Unless you want to hang around.
除非你想留下來 是嗎？
I'll let you play with my duck.
對，你可以跟我的鴨子玩
Stripper!
跳脫衣舞的
The stripper stole the ring!
舞孃把戒指偷走了
Chandler,get up! The stripper stole the ring!
錢德，起床 舞孃把戒指偷走了
-What? -The ring is gone!
什麼？ 戒指被偷了
Just give me a minute to wake up for this.
先讓我清醒一下
You lost the ring. You're the worst best man!
你把戒指弄丟了 你是最爛的伴郎
This isn't funny. I go to sleep,everything's cool.
不好笑，怎麼辦？ 我去睡覺，一切正常
I wake up,the stripper's gone, and the ring is gone!
等我醒來，舞孃不見了 戒指也不見了
-You slept with her? -Of course!
你跟她上床？ 廢話
-Hi,guys. -Hi,Phoebe.
你們兩個 菲比
I wanted to apologize if I seemed a tad edgy yesterday at my shower.
我想說聲抱歉 我昨天在送禮會上似乎凶了點
Just the hormones.
荷爾蒙作祟
-No,we -Hormones.
別這樣，我們…  荷爾蒙嘛
I wanted to say thank you. It was so sweet.
謝謝你們，你們真有心
You seem to be doing much better.
你似乎好多了，太好了
-How are things going? -Good.
你現在怎樣？ 很好
Everything's been about me lately. So what's happening with you?
最近的注意力都在我 你們呢？
We were just talking about me not going to Ross' wedding.
我們正在說 我不去參加羅斯的婚禮
It just might be too hard, given the history and all that.
有那段過往 我可能很難面對
This reminds me of the time when I lived on the street.
這讓我想起當年流落街頭時
This guy offered to buy me food if I slept with him.
有人說我陪他上床就請我吃飯
How is this like that?
這兩件事哪裡像？
Well,let's see. It's not really like that.
我想想…的確不像
Because that was an actual problem.
因為那才算是問題
And yours is just a bunch of high-school crap...
你這只是高中女生無病呻吟
...that nobody really gives!
沒人在乎
I'm sorry. I just thought
抱歉，我只是…
Here come the water works.
淚眼攻勢來了
I called the company that sent her, and they don't care.
我已經沒轍了 我打給仲介站，他們不管
I called 911 and they yelled at me. This is an emergency!
我打119又被吼 這還不算緊急事件嗎？
I really wanna help you out, but I got plans to go see Titanic...
我真的很想幫忙 但我打算去看「鐵達尼號」
...so I've got to call 911 to find out what time it starts.
所以我要打119問場次
Hey,guys.
我來了
Thanks again for last night. What a great party.
謝謝你，派對辦得很棒
The guys from work had a blast.
博物館那夥人玩得很爽
One of them had never been to a bachelor party before.
其中有一個沒參加過單身派對
Another one had never been to a party before.
另一個沒參加過派對
So that wedding ring.
那個結婚戒指
-Man,that is nice. -Yeah,right?
可真漂亮 漂亮吧
I might pick one of those babies up for myself.
我也想買一個
Where might one get one of those?
要去哪裡買？
When my grandmother first came to this country...
那個戒指？ 我奶奶剛來到這個國家時
...that ring and the clothes on her back were all she had with her.
全身上下只有那只戒指 和一小包衣服
So you might say that the ring is irreplaceable.
所以那只戒指可說是無可取代
Absolutely. It's been in my family for generations.
當然，它是我家的傳家寶
Every bride who's worn it has lived a long and happy life.
每個戴上它的新娘 都能幸福到老
So you might say it's a magic ring.
所以簡直算是一隻魔戒
Yeah,the stripper stole it.
被脫衣舞孃偷了
What?
什麼？
-What did you just -I think I heard what he said.
你剛才說… 我想我聽到了
I believe it was, "The stripper stole the ring."
應該是說… 「被脫衣舞孃偷了」
My ring? My wedding ring?
偷了我的戒指？我的結婚戒指？
The stripper stole my wedding ring?
脫衣舞孃偷了我的結婚戒指？
How could this happen?
怎麼會這樣？
It all started when you said, "Joey,you be my best man!"
原因就在於你說了 「喬伊，你來當我的伴郎吧」
All right. I'm going to call the cops.
好，我來報警
I screwed up. But you don't have to turn me in.
我搞砸了你也不用報官捉我
-Not on you,on the stripper. -I already did that.
不是捉你，是捉那個舞孃 我試過了
They said they'd look into it after they solve all the murders.
他們說等偵破所有謀殺案再說
-We'll call the company that sent her. -I did that too.
那就找仲介站 我也試過了
They wouldn't give me her real name.
他們不肯透露她的真名或電話
They said if I bother them again, they'd call the police.
他們說我再打去就要報警
I said,"You talk to the police, you tell them I'm missing a ring."
我說「你去啊」 「就說我掉了一隻戒指」
So,what are you telling me?
There's nothing we can do?
難道一點辦法也沒有？
-How could this happen? -Look,Ross,I am so sorry.
怎麼會這樣？ 羅斯，我真的很抱歉
What if we just called her...
我們可以再叫她一次
...used a fake name and had her come to my office?
用假名把她找去我的辦公室
That sounds like fun, but we got a ring to find!
好像不賴，但我們得找戒指
Here's your tea,Phoebe.
菲比，你的茶
It's so good.
感覺真好
Thanks.
謝謝
-Good. -So glad you like it.
那就好 你喜歡就好
What? She made the tea.
怎樣？茶是她泡的
I think I just had a contraction.
不是，我剛才陣痛了
-What? -My God!
什麼？ 天哪
I felt one a few minutes ago.
幾分鐘前就有一次
That definitely was one.
這次絕對錯不了
You can't have the baby here.
你不能在這裡生
I haven't sterilized the apartment since the guys moved out!
男生搬走之後我還沒消毒
It's okay. I'll boil some water and rip up some sheets.
沒事，別怕，我來燒水撕床單
It's probably false labor.
別緊張，可能是假性陣痛
That can happen near the end. Just get the book.
接近預產期會這樣，去拿書來
-Get the book! -The book!
瑞秋，拿書來 書，好
-The Bible? -I don't know!
聖經？ 我哪知啊
All right. This is great.
好，很好
You get behind the desk.
錢德，你站到桌子後面
When she comes in, she won't recognize you because
但願她一進來不會認得你 因為…
Well,why would she?
她怎麼會認得你
And then you buzz Ross and l.
然後你對羅斯和我打暗號
You be Mr. Gonzales, and I'll be Mr. Wong.
你是岡薩勒斯先生 我是王先生
Diverse.
民族大鎔爐
Anybody call for security?
有人叫警衛嗎？
You be cool.
冷靜
Which one is Gunther Central Perk?
好，哪位是阿甘中央咖啡館？
Joey.
喬伊
Where's my ring? My dead grandmother's wedding ring.
我的戒指呢？ 我過世的奶奶的結婚戒指呢？
Way to be cool,man.
你還真冷靜
What?
你在說什麼？
There was a ring in a box. After you left,it was gone.
床頭櫃的絲絨盒裡有只戒指 你一走它就不見了
You think I stole some ring?
你們覺得我偷了戒指？
We know you took it! Just save yourself the time and confess.
一定是你偷的 少廢話，從實招來
Who are you,the Hardy Boys?
你們是少年偵探團嗎？
I don't need to steal a stupid ring. I make $1,600 a week.
我不必偷什麼戒指 我1星期賺1600
Any of you guys make that?
你們有人賺那麼多嗎？
Marry me.
嫁給我
I don't get it. It was in my room all night. She didn't take it.
我不懂，戒指整晚都在我房裡
I didn't take it. You didn't take it. Then who did?
她沒拿，我沒拿，你沒拿 那是誰拿的？
We're trying to think.
安靜，我們在想事情
I don't get how you know it's false labor.
你怎麼會知道是假痛？
Do you see any babies?
你有看到寶寶嗎？
-How do you feel? -Okay,I guess.
你感覺如何？ 還好吧
I don't know.
我不知道
I know it's going to be over soon so....
大概是知道快要結束了
But isn't that a good thing?
那不是很好嗎？
-You said you were sick of this. -I know.
你說你受夠了 我知道
Usually,when you're done with the pregnant thing...
只是通常懷孕完之後
...you get to do the mom thing.
就是當媽媽
But I'll be sitting around in my leather pants,drinking tequila.
我卻會穿著皮褲喝龍舌蘭
Some moms do that.
有些媽媽也會那樣
That's even sadder.
那樣更悲慘
Look,I know what I got myself into.
我知道這麼做的後果
It's just that now that they're in me...
但他們現在在我肚子裡
...it's like I know them and....
我彷彿瞭解他們
It just won't be easy when these babies have to go away.
把他們送走時我會很難受
I know,sweetie.
我知道
But it's not like you won't have anything.
但你並不會一無所有
You'll have nieces and nephews. That's even better.
你會有姪子姪女 那樣甚至更棒
-Yeah,okay. -No,really.
少來 不，是真的
You won't be the one worrying about saving for college.
你不必擔心他們的大學學費
Or yelling at them when they're bad.
或在他們不乖時罵他們
Or putting them on Ritalin when they just won't calm down.
或在他們吵個不停時 餵他們吃立得寧
You'll be the one they run away to. The one they talk to about sex.
他們逃家會來找你 會找你討論性的問題
You just get to be cool Aunt Phoebe.
你可以當酷阿姨菲比
Cool Aunt Phoebe.
酷阿姨菲比
I am pretty cool.
我是蠻酷的
And you know what else? Are they going to love you!
還有，他們一定會愛死你
They are going to love me.
他們會愛死我
Thanks,you guys. Again.
謝謝你們…再次感謝
Oh,sweetie.
謝什麼
Thanks.
謝謝
What?
怎麼了？
Just kidding.
開玩笑的
Oh,my God!
怎麼了？ 天哪
Got you again. You're so easy!
又騙到了，你們真好騙
If anything happens to him
要是它有事…
The vet said it's a simple procedure.
喬伊，獸醫說手術很簡單
Things can go wrong. What if he doesn't make it?
所以呢？搞不好會出錯 要是它沒撐過來呢？
-He will,Joe. -But what if he doesn't?
它會的 要是沒有呢？
He's such a good duck.
它這麼乖巧
I'm so worried about him!
我好擔心它
Somebody lose a ring?
有人掉了戒指嗎？
Oh,my God! Thank you! Thank you so much!
天哪！謝謝你，謝謝
How's the duck?
鴨子怎麼樣？
Just fine. You'll see him in a bit.
它很好，正在休息 你們可以去見它
Great.
太好了
-Thanks for being so cool. -No,that's all right.
羅斯，謝謝你這麼好脾氣 沒關係 當然有關係
You made me your best man and I totally let you down.
你找我當伴郎，我卻讓你失望
-It's not your fault. -Yeah,it is.
又不是你的錯 當然是
You wouldn't have lost it.
你就不會弄丟戒指
Ross,you were right. He should be your best man.
你知道嗎？羅斯，你是對的 他才應該當你的伴郎
-No,you should. -Don't argue.
不，應該你當 別吵了
I get to choose my best man.
伴郎是我選的
I want both you guys.
你們兩個我都要
Really?
真的？
Both you guys should be up there with me.
你們都應該陪我站在神父面前
You two are my
你們是我的…
I'm lucky to have just one good
有一個好朋友就…
Thanks,man.
謝了
I got to go check something,okay?
我去那邊看看
-What a baby! -Total wuss.
真孩子氣 有夠愛哭的
-How come you're getting Nana's ring? -Mom gave it to me.
為什麼奶奶的戒指是給你？ 是媽給我的
She said something about it being a wedding ring and that you may not need...
她說有個婚戒比較大 你又可能...
...one.
...用不上
I really didn't need to tell you all that.
我實在不必說這些
I don't really think it's fair. I mean,I've always loved that ring.
我覺得不公平 我一直很喜歡那個戒指
Oh,Mon,I'm sorry.
對不起
I'd let you have it, but Emily's gotten really attached to it.
我原本會讓給你 但艾蜜莉對它愛不釋手
Thanks.
好吧 謝謝
-Here you go. -Thanks.
拿去 謝謝
Emily,did you know that that ring spent two days in a duck's colon?
你知道那個戒指 在鴨子肚子裡擺了2天嗎？